Now another thing that you can do with your wax is use it as a decorative effect.
The way that that works, you go ahead and put the wax where it's needed on the pot.
In this case, on the bottom.
Now clearly we don't need the wax resist anywhere else on this pot, but what you can do is take your brush, load it up with your hot wax and make a design on the pot.
It can be anything.
It could be just little squiggles, you can draw an actual character, anything you have interest to put on there.
And what this is going to do is when you go to dip this pot in the glaze, which I'll demonstrate in a moment, this glaze will resist, I mean this wax will resist the glaze.
You'll be left with bare clay anywhere that you've brushed this wax.
But what's kind of cool about it is usually, your glaze is going to have kind of a halo edge around every place where it stops.
So you'll have your glaze, a little bit of a halo seeping into the wax area, and then these nice decorative areas that you've left blank.
Which in this case, will turn dark brown.